And we're going to go over another upper body stretch while you are on the ground.
So we just did the cat stretch and now we're going to do a variation of that stretch getting more of the lats.
And the lats are the wings on the side of your body.
Alright, so getting on your, you?re on your knees, both knees, both hands, you're like in the, good solid sturdy position.
Now if I'm going to stretch out my right lat, I'm going to drop, I'm going to bring my left shoulder closer to my left hip, while trying to bring my right shoulder further away from my right hip, therefore really increasing the distance between these two points.
That and at the same time I'm going to be twisting my hips to even greater the distance away from my hip to my shoulder.
So by doing that I'm really going to feel that stretch in the lower lat all the way up to the upper part of my lats, or the wings on the side of my body.
So the stretch will look like this.
And you can do that on the, on the other side as well too.
And that's another lat stretch.